《闪电侠》本季回顾
This season on "The Flash"...
迪沃和他妻子是超级大坏蛋
DeVoe and his wife are super villains.
他创造了12个超能力者
He created 12 meta-humans
好让他窃取其超能力
just so he could steal their powers.
这是你们的一员吗  拉尔夫·德比
This was your team member, Ralph Dibny.
一个菜鸟英雄
A rookie hero.
我会来救你的
I'll save you!
我的丈夫已经死了
My husband is dead.
我要离开你了  克利福德
I'm leaving you, Clifford.
这是智力增强器
This is an intelligence booster.
你的大脑重启了
Your mind is being rebooted.
我越多地想要使用我的大脑
The more I try to use my brains,
我就会越快失去它
the sooner I'm going to lose it.
迪沃计划把他的五颗卫星
DeVoe plans to position
分别发射到绕地球轨道的特定位置
each of his five satellites around the globe.
卫星为了一个目的同时运行
Satellites working together for a single purpose?
迪沃想要移除地球上
DeVoe wants to remove the intelligence
所有人的智慧
of everyone on earth.
要有光
Let there be light.
我是巴里  请留言
Hey, it's Barry. Leave a message.
艾伦  我是辛格队长
Allen, Captain Singh.
你拿回工作这事有好消息了
Got some good news about you getting your job back.
你也可以感谢你妻子
You can thank your wife, too.
显然市长看了爱瑞丝写的
Apparently the Mayor read all those posts Iris wrote
那些说迪沃的帖子  她决定
about DeVoe, and she's decided--
巴里·艾伦
主动呼叫
闪 电 侠
第四季
第二十三集
-西斯科  我们需要能源  -正在解决
- Cisco, we need power! - Working on it.
一切都失灵了  连手机都用不了
Nothing is working. Not even cell phones.
这正是我担心的事情
That's what I was worried about.
开始了  是不是
It's happening isn't it?
我不知道  我们的计划失败了
I don't know. I mean, our plan didn't work.
迪沃用尖端科研实验室的卫星
DeVoe replaced the satellite I destroyed
代替了我毁掉的那颗卫星
with the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
来开启大悟之道
to set off The Enlightenment.
巴仔  外面都疯了
Bar, it's going nuts out there.
到处都失去了能源  我们的车都发动不了
There is no power anywhere. Our car just stopped working.
谢天谢地我们离得近
Thank God we were close by.
医院可还得多走三英里远呢
I mean, the hospital is another three miles away.
医院
The hospital?
-乔  -天变成紫色了
- Joe? - The sky turned purple,
并且她开始宫缩了
and she started having contractions
-西斯科  快点  -要是我们没法带她
- Cisco, hurry! - If we're not able to get her
去医院  你能不能...
to the hospital can you use--
不  巴里不能带她跑
No, Barry can't run her.
对塞西尔和宝宝都不安全
It is not safe for Cecile or the baby.
那我们要怎么办
Then what are we gonna do?
这里有一切接生需要的设备
I have everything here I'd need to deliver a baby.
什么
What?
-谢天谢地  -太棒了
- Thank God. - Great.
让我们看看你产道开得如何了
Uh, let's go see how dilated you are.
呼吸  宝贝  呼吸
Breathe, baby, breathe.
有东西需要你来看一下
You're gonna want to see this.
迪沃肯定预料到哈里会制造一个
DeVoe must to predicted Harry would build
他自己的思考帽并且用
his own thinking cap and power it
这管子里的暗物质驱动
with the dark matter from this tube.
他可以从尖端实验室把暗物质虹吸出去
Dark matter that he could then siphon off
然后用来感染整个世界
from S.T.A.R. Labs to use to infect the world.
哈里是他的小白鼠  他知道要是他可以
Harry was his guinea pig. He knew if he could reboot
重启哈里的大脑  他就可以重启所有人的
Harry's brain, he could reboot everyone's.
吉迪恩呢  她能黑进那些卫星吗
What about Gideon, could she hack into the satellites?
不行  紫色光晕也让她下线了
No, purple haze took her out too.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
我不知道
I don't know.
没关系  巴里
It's okay, Barry.
我知道怎么做
I think I do.
我也和各位一样都喜欢《盗梦空间》
Look, I love "Inception" As much as the next guy,
但把巴里送进迪沃的大脑
but sending Barry into DeVoe's mind?
只有他的大脑快得足以
His mind is the only one fast enough
承受链接并且不受任何伤害
to survive the linking process without any harm.
但这个怎么就能帮助我们阻止他
Yeah, but how would this help us to stop him?
要是我们能找到迪沃心中残存的善意
If we can find the good left in Clifford
并且帮助它重新控制他的大脑
and help it retake control of his mind,
善就能胜过恶
that good could overpower the bad.
你认为他体内还有残存的善
You think there actually is good left inside him?
我知道这很难想像
I know that this is hard to imagine,
但克利福德曾经是个彻头彻尾的好人
but there was a time when Clifford was nothing but good,
那时他只想帮助世界
when he truly wanted to help the world.
是注入他大脑的暗物质改变了他
It's the dark matter he infused in his brain that changed him.
是的  我相信他还有善良的一面
So yes, I do believe that there is some good in him.
我们只是需要找到它
Someway we just need to find it.
简直是疯了
This is crazy.
我们为什么不直接打电话给我们信任的人
I mean, why don't we just call someone we trust?
卡拉  奥利弗  沃利
Kara, Oliver, Wally...
你可以把你的友军都叫来
You could bring a legion of your friends,
但他们根本不是对手
but they would pose no challenge.
克利福德创造出公车超能力者
Clifford created the bus metas
并将这些超能力的组合
and the combination of the abilities
来确保他能够击败
to ensure that he could defeat anyone
所有会帮助你的人
whose assistance you might enlist.
距离我们的大脑清零还有多久
How long until our minds are wiped?
在渗透网达到百分之百的时候
We'll have it until the permeation grid hits 100%.
渗透网
我们要怎么进入他的大脑
How would we get me inside his mind?
我们要想办法把你的意识传输到他的大脑里
We need to find a way to transfer your consciousness into his.
不  你知道我每次想用震波感应他都会有事
No, you know what happens every time I try to vibe him.
-我做不到  -我可以
- I-I-I can't do it. - I do.
但是我们需要的不是你的超能力  拉蒙先生
But I don't think it's your power we need, Mr. Ramon.
而是她的
I believe it's hers.
这样会增强霍尔顿女士的心灵感应能力
This will amplify Ms. Horton's telepathic ability
把闪电侠的意识和克利福德的连接在一起
to link The Flash's consciousness to Clifford's,
不管他在哪里
wherever he may be.
这也有可能提供了单相连接
It could also provide a one-way link
他就不会发现有人进入了他的大脑了
so that he doesn't realize that someone is inside his mind.
所以这算是某种单向脑电波吗
So it's kind like a one-way brain radio.
应该是的  没错
I suppose so, yes.
听到了吗  哈里
Hey, hear that, Harry?
你的大脑抑制器会得到充分的利用
That cerebral inhibitor of yours is going to be put to good use.
我为你的朋友感到难过  他的大脑有可能会
I'm sorry about your friend. His mind could--
难过是不会让他好起来的
Sorry won't make him better. Will it?
-万事俱备了吗  -应该是的
- Everything ready? - Think so.
艾伦先生  椅子
Mr. Allen, the chair.
霍尔顿女士  轮床
Ms. Horton, the gurney.
你要让他坐在那椅子上吗
You want to put him in that thing?
只有这样才能建立霍尔顿女士
It is the only way to establish a transcranial link
和艾伦先生的经颅连接
between Ms. Horton and Mr. Allen.
乔  我不会有事的
Joe, I'll be all right.
我会一直陪在你们身边的
I'll be here the whole time.
我们知道
We know.
艾伦先生  把帽子戴在头上
Mr. Allen, put the cap on your head.
一旦塞西尔锁定了迪沃的脑波
Once Cecile has locked on to DeVoe's brain waves,
我们会把你的意识传输至扁桃体
we'll transfer your consciousness to his amygdala.
那就是大脑
That's the part of the brain
情感意义与记忆相连接的部分
that connects emotional significance to memories.
美好的记忆就在那里
Where the good memories are,
我们会找到克利福德善良的一面的
we will find the good part of Clifford.
开始了  霍尔顿女士
Here we go, Ms. Horton...
巴里
Barry?
没事吧
Is everything okay?
这是在逗我呢吗
You've gotta be kidding me.
各位  我进来了
Guys, I'm in.
描述一下  你看到些什么  身边有些什么
Paint the picture. What do you see? What's around you?
首先  我看到了思考者
For starters, The Thinker.
我在405路公车上  就在路中央
I'm in the 405 bus, in the middle of the street.
我刚从之前那个传送门里出来了
I just came out of that same portal from before.
那里就是一切开始的地方
This is where it all began.
那是克利福德的大脑中心
It is the nexus of Clifford's brain.
一旦你找到他  把他带过去
Once you find him, get him through it,
他就能重新控制他的思想了
and he can regain control of his mind.
他需要找些什么
Okay, what does he need to look for?
我们的家
Our house.
好的
All right.
巴里  你看到些什么
Barry, what do you see?
什么也没有
Nothing.
这描述对外边的观众来说比较模糊
A little vague for the viewers at home.
什么叫做什么也没有
What do you mean "Nothing"?
我是说家里是空的
I mean it's empty.
家里空荡荡的
It is completely empty.
好吧  我该去哪...
All right, well, where should I go--
巴里  巴里  听到我说话吗
Barry? Barry, can you hear me?
思考帽
宝贝  喘气
Babe, breathe.
塞西尔的超能力连接着她的妊娠
Cecile's powers are connected to her pregnancy.
宫缩肯定肯定给她的经颅连接
Her contractions must be putting a strain
造成了压力
on her transcranial link.
不不不  这点我们要想想办法
No, no, no. We need to do something about that.
我们不能不让她生孩子啊  马尔利泽
We can't stop her from having a baby, Marlize.
只能如此  韦斯特艾伦女士
We have to, Mrs. West-Allen,
不然就无法起作用了
or this will never work.
只有她才能让巴里
She is the only way to get Barry
出入克利福德的大脑
in and out of Clifford's mind.
所有人冷静  又不是说塞西尔
Everyone chill; it's not like Cecile is going to lose
生了孩子之后就会失去能力
her powers if she has this baby.
塞西尔生了孩子之后就会失去能力
Cecile is going to lose her powers if she has this baby?
这不就把巴里困在迪沃的脑袋里了
Won't that leave Barry stranded in DeVoe's mind?
恐怕是这样
I'm afraid so.
你不觉得这种信息应该早早的
Information you may have wanted to share,
就该跟我们分享吗
like, way before now.
乔  你还有我给你的那个吸入器吗
Joe, do you still have that inhaler I gave you?
有  在我们医院的包里
Yeah, it's in our hospital bag.
好  大部分吸入器含有特布他林
Okay, most inhalers contain the drug terbutaline,
可以用来放缓宫缩
which can be used to slow down contractions.
我找到托马斯了
I found Thomas.
他一直都是这样
He's been this way all the time.
这是说的什么
What the hell is all about?
我不知道  我得去找吸入器了
I--I don't know... I'm going to get the inhaler.
-西斯科  替我下  -好
- Cisco, cover me. - Yeah.
各位  咱们得告诉巴里下一步去哪里
Guys, we need to tell Barry where to go next.
要尽快  哈里找到马尔利泽在哪里了
And fast. Harry figured out where Marlize was.
也许他可以
Maybe he can--
哈里
Harry?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
帮我
Help.
不
No.
不能让你把剩下的脑细胞都烧掉
You are not frying away what's left of you.
帮我
Help!
Help.
求你
Please.
看到没
See?
什么都没有
Nothing.
拉蒙
Ramon.
迪沃第一次爱上马尔利泽的地方
Where DeVoe first fell in love with Marlize.
叫巴里去那里
Tell Barry to go there.
你可以在那里找到他
You'll find him there.
好吗
Okay?
好的
Okay.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
星群  如此渺小
Stars, so little.
我们不应该在这里
We shouldn't be here.
我今天不想再失去任何人
I won't lose anyone else today.
绝对不会
I won't.
哈里的点子  去牛津大学
Harry had an idea. Go to Oxford.
牛津大学
Oxford?
波尔斯山下的小村庄
The hamlet of Boars Hill.
我们相爱的地方
The place where we fell in love.
好的  我这就去
All right, I'm on my way.
我到了
I'm here.
这里有个毯子  一些酒
There is a blanket, some wine...
车载收音机放着音乐
There's a song playing on a car radio.
我们的第一次跳舞
Our first dance.
迪沃呢
And DeVoe?
他不在这里
He's not here.
好吧  各位...
All right guys, well...
下面去哪里
where to next?
菜鸟
Rookie?
艾伦  你在这里做什么
Allen? What are you doing here?
拉尔夫  真的是你吗
Ralph? Is that really you?
我以为我失去你了
I thought I lost you.
真对不起  老兄  我...
I'm so sorry, man. I--
我也很想你  巴里
I missed you too, Barry.
巴里  你刚才是说了  拉尔夫吗
Barry, did you just say, Ralph?
是啊  各位  是拉尔夫
Yes, guys. Yeah, it's Ralph.
他  他还活着
He's--he's alive.
等下  你是怎么出现在这里的
Wait, how are you even here?
你又是怎么到这里的
How are you here?
迪沃是不是  他是不是也吸收你了
Did DeVoe--did he get you?
不  不  他没有
No, no, he didn't.
他  塞西尔用她的心灵感应
He-Cecile is using her telepathy
把我的意识传送到了迪沃脑中
to get my consciousness inside DeVoe's mind.
真玄乎
That's trippy.
为什么
Why?
我们得找到他内心好的一部分
We need to find the good part of him
来阻止他坏的那部分开启大悟之道
so we can stop the bad from starting the Enlightenment.
你看到过他吗
Have you seen him?
一个好迪沃
A good DeVoe?
没有
No.
只有邪恶悬浮椅状态的
Just the evil, floating chair variety.
他总是来找我
He visits me all the time.
他知道你在这里吗
He knows you're here?
他为什么要...
Why would he need to--
在这里我随心所欲  艾伦先生
In this place I do as I please, Mr. Allen.
我得说  你居然以为
I must say, the fact that you thought
我预测不到你和你小队进行这种
I wouldn't have calculated you and your team making
没用的尝试  真是有些侮辱人
this feeble attempt is somewhat insulting.
没有什么能击败本年度的大坏蛋  艾伦先生
There will be not defeating the big bad this year, Mr. Allen.
看  你在我的大脑里了
See, you are in my mind now.
已经逃无可逃
And there's no escape.
跑  艾伦先生  跑吧
Run, Mr. Allen, run.
巴里
Barry?
连接丢失
巴里
Barry!
他冲我们来了
He's--he's coming for us.
他冲我们来了  我听到他的想法了
He's coming for us. I heard his thoughts.
他来了  他要来这里了
He's coming. He's coming here.
-我们得离开这里  -去哪里
- We need to leave. - And go where?
我们要做什么
Okay, what do we doing?
我要救你出去
I'm getting you out of here.
但我们还得找到好的迪沃
We still need to find the good DeVoe, though.
怎么做
How?
他肯定在某个对他有特殊意义的地方
He's gonna be someplace that means something to him.
在他成为现在这样之前的地方
Before he became who he is now.
是说他还是一位单纯的历史教授的时候吗
You mean like when he was a simple history professor?
星星在陨落
Stars are raining.
得走了  快
Got to go! Come on.
好
Good.
今天我们齐聚在此用一首歌来敬神
We are gathered here today to worship in song.
我建议用"到这里来吧"[传统圣歌]
I suggest "Kumbaya."
力场
A force field.
立场  笨蛋
Force field, sucker.
我就不该让你们在我的监督之外
I should never have let you build this chair
造这把椅子
without my oversight.
这是我第一次计算失误
It was my first miscalculation.
你计算失误了很多次
You've made many miscalculations.
是吗
Really?
你思考过我为何不追逐闪电侠吗
Have you ever pondered why I never pursued The Flash?
为何从不需要他的速度或大脑
Never needed his speed or his mind?
有人想过吗
Anyone?
他与神速力的连接
His connection to the Speed Force.
能进入所有时间  过去现在未来的能力
Access to all of time-- past, present, future.
真知
True knowledge.
既然你们已经把他放在我的大脑里
And now that you have placed him inside my mind,
我就拥有了一切
I'll have it all.
你得先找到我们
You'll have to find us first.
迪沃的巢穴  你疯了吗
DeVoe's lair? Are you crazy?
他能在这个口袋维度发现我们吗
Can he find us in this pocket dimension?
我为我们争取了点时间
I've bought us some time.
时间  节奏  飞翔  旁边
Time...rhyme... fly...side.
塞西尔  我们需要你尝试再次与巴里连接
Cecile, we need you to try and link up with Barry again.
我试试
I'll try.
迪沃教授
Professor DeVoe?
巴里
Barry?
巴里  能听到我吗
Barry, can you hear me?
可以  爱瑞丝  我能听到你
Yeah. Yeah, Iris, I hear you.
怎么了
What's wrong?
好迪沃  我们找到他了
Good DeVoe, we found him.
他已经死了
He's dead.
我猜你没有其他计划了  对吧
I don't suppose you have another plan, do you?
没有了  就是这样了
No, man. I mean, I--this was it.
现在
Now--
现在世界属于思考者的了
Now the world belongs to the Thinker.
艾伦  听我说
Allen, listen to me.
我困在这里了
I'm stuck here,
但你没有
but you're not.
你应该离开
You should go.
在仅剩的时间里和家人相守
Be with your family for whatever time is left.
不
No.
首先  是我们的家人
Okay, first of all, it's our family,
我不会丢下你不管的
and I'm not leaving you behind.
肯定还有别的方法
There's gotta be another way.
艾伦  你说过拯救世界唯一的方法
Allen, you said the only way to save the world
就是找到迪沃心中好的一面
is by finding the good that's left in DeVoe.
他就在这里
It's right here.
胸口上中了一枪
With a hole in its chest.
这不是他心中唯一的善
It's not the only good left in him.
怎么刹车了  我们到了吗
Why the brakes? Are we there?
快到了
Almost.
那就是地狱之口吗
So that's the Hellmouth?
那是迪沃的精神联结
That's the nexus of DeVoe's mind.
马尔利泽说如果迪沃心中善穿过这里
Marlize said we can take control of him if the good in DeVoe
我们就能控制他
passes through it.
艾伦  我们知道这不可能
Allen, we know that's not possible anymore.
你觉得他为什么让你活下来
Why do you think he's keeping you alive?
我不知道是为什么  但是想一想
I couldn't figure it out, but think about it.
如果你逃出去  你就会重新控制这具身体
If you get out, you take back control of this body,
因为这是你的
because it's yours.
这就是他为什么不让你离开
That's why he won't let you leave.
一旦你逃出去  迪沃就不复存在了
Once you get out, DeVoe will cease to exist.
你需要做的  就是让它穿过那个传送门
All you have to do is make it through that portal,
然后你就会重新获得控制
and you'll regain control.
记住你是谁  拉尔夫
Remember who you are, Ralph.
一个英雄
A hero.
我们去夺回控制
Let's go get control.
或者我杀了你怎么样
Or how about I kill you?
再一次  如果有必要的话
A second time if necessary.
怎么回事
What was that?
是我丈夫
My husband.
他越来越近了
He's getting close.
拜托告诉我还有人也感觉到了
Please tell me someone else felt that.
抱歉
Apologies.
我不得不紧急转移到另一个口袋维度
I had to force an emergency shift to another pocket dimension.
会有些不安
It can be unnerving.
心安  服务  迂回  弯曲
Nerving, serving, swerving, curving.
没事的
Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
怎么了
What's wrong?
无法再拖了  你感觉怎么样  塞西尔
No more labor suppression. How you feeling, Cecile?
我不知道我能不能做到
Like--like I don't know if I can do this.
你本来不需要这样做的
You shouldn't have to.
你本可以像其他母亲那样
You should be able to have our baby just like any other parent,
在医院的床上分娩
in a hospital, in a regular bed,
而不是像现在这样
not with all this.
看看你对我们的朋友都做了些什么
Hey, look what you've done to our friend,
对我的儿子  我的女儿  我今生的挚爱
my son, my daughter, the love of my life,
对这座城市里的每一个人
everybody in this damn city.
-爸爸  -你怎么能觉得
- Dad-- - How could you ever think
这样做会让人类变得更好
that this would be better for humanity?
爸爸  巴里从神速力出来的时候
Dad, what did you say to me when Barry came out
你对我说了什么
of the Speed Force?
你说  "没有信仰的力量是没有意义的"
You said, "Strength without faith means nothing."
我们要有信心能够共同克服这些困难
We need to have faith that we can get through this together.
他要多久能找到我们
How long until he finds us?
几分钟  或者更快
Minutes, maybe less.
我了个去  我打不到他
Crap in a hat. I can't hit him.
他们知道我们在想什么
They can read our minds.
那我们就用德比风格战斗
Then we do this Dibny-style.
-什么  -我们不思考
- What? - We don't think.
用别的东西填充你的大脑
Just fill your mind with something else.
想想你爱的那些
Something you love.
拉尔夫
Ralph.
全虾自助餐
Shrimp buffet!
你和我一起  爱瑞丝
It's you and me, Iris.
大虾拼盘  鸡尾冷虾
Shrimp platter! Shrimp cocktail!
炸板虾
beignets de crevettes.
再来一次  艾伦先生  你还不够好
Once again, Mr. Allen, your best will not be good enough.
有什么计划  菜鸟
What's the plan, Rookie?
我想不出其它鲜虾大餐了
I'm running out of shrimp entrees.
你只需要一个
Well, you're only gonna need one.
现在宫缩五分钟一次
They're coming every five minutes.
星星在陨落
The stars are raining...
塞西尔  拜托先集中精力不要生下宝宝
Cecile, please just focus on not having a baby.
星星在陨落  枯竭  痛苦
Stars are raining, draining, painting.
他听起来像巴里从神速力出来的时候
He sounds just like Barry when he came out of the Speed Force.
是的  我知道
Yeah, I know.
不  我是说他现在说的话和当时完全相同
No, I mean, he's saying the exact same words.
你应该注意一下枪口的方向
You should mind where you point your weapon,
韦斯特警探
Detective West.
离我的女孩们远点
Stay away from my girls.
乔
Joe!
进攻的克隆人
Hey, attack of the clones,
快过来抓我
come and get me.
坚持住
Hang on!
太厉害了
That was awesome.
走吧
Come on.
现在结束了
Now it ends.
你是怎么打败我的
How did you beat me?
不是我  是我们
I didn't. We did.
她们对德比先生的眷恋
Their emotional attachment to Mr. Dibny have made them
使他们比你更强大  克利福德
stronger than you would ever be, Clifford.
但是  你不会懂
But then, you wouldn't understand.
不  这不是我的意愿
No! This is not my will!
再也不了  是我的意愿
Not anymore. It's mine.
数字还在增加
Numbers are still rising.
克利福德的超能力
Clifford's meta-abilities
不再控制每一个卫星
are no longer controlling each satellite.
如果我能重写他们最后一个命令
If I can just override their last command.
快
Come on.
渗透电网
整个城市里不再有暗能量了
There's no more dark energy anywhere in the city.
我们做到了
We did it.
我的弹某某
Oh, my stretchy so-and-so.
各位
Uh, guys...
我羊水刚刚破了
my water just broke.
我们赶紧把她送到医务室
Let's get her to the Med Lab. Quickly.
-好的  -要生了
- Okay. - Baby's coming.
-天呐  要生了  -小心  小心点
- Oh, boy, baby's coming. - Careful. Carefully.
走吧  哈里
Come on, Harry.
求你  告诉我你以前做过这个
Please, tell me you've done this before.
有几次  在医学院
A few times. In med school.
医
Med--
-医学院  -是啊
- Med school? - Yeah.
好吧  医学院  好吧
Okay. Med school. Okay.
乔  放松就好
Joe, just relax.
我们能搞定  对吧
We got this. Right?
对  只要呼气
Yeah, just breath out.
只要呼气
Just breath out.
电力全面恢复了
Power's back on everywhere.
现在世界终于能恢复正常了
Now the world can finally get back to normal.
站立  翻滚  旋转  坠落  坠落
Standing, tossing, turning, falling, falling...
他怎么了
What happened to him?
他开悟了
He is enlightened.
迪肯先生电力的另一种用途
Another use of Mr. Deacon's powers.
技术复生
Technological reincarnation.
-西斯科  -他正在接管
- Cisco. - He's taking over.
我告诉过你  大悟之道
I told you that The Enlightenment
将会为你而来  马尔利泽  那它就会
will come for you, Marlize, and it will.
记住  我一切都想到了
Remember, I thought of everything.
甚至此刻
Even this moment.
再见  我的爱人
Good-bye, my love.
我们又连接上了
We're back online.
不仅如此
Not just that.
卫星进入衰减轨道
Satellite's in a decaying orbit.
等等  所以马尔利泽对他的拆除
Wait, so Marlize deactivating him
触发了对已死之人的转换
triggered a literal dead man's switch?
它在快速坠落
It's falling fast.
克利福德一定已经把它的质量增加了一千倍
Clifford must've increased its mass by a thousand-fold.
巴里  那种又沉又快的东西的冲击力
Barry, the impact of something that heavy
我们还有多少时间
and that fast-- How much time do we have?
三分钟  幸运的话
Three minutes if we are lucky.
好吧  我们如何阻止一个
Okay, how do we stop something that is going to
撞击时间
三分钟
灾难级别
灭绝
将要把我们送回石器时代的东西
send us back into the stone age?
一起  我会散播消息来疏散市区
Together. I'll spread the word to evacuate downtown.
拉尔夫  西斯科  你们清理冲击区域
Ralph, Cisco, you guys clear the impact zone.
巴里  你得毁掉那颗卫星
Barry, you've gotta destroy that satellite.
好了  现在是时候推了
Okay, now it's time for you to push.
数到三
On three.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
你做的很棒
You're doing great.
往那边走  女士  不是这边
Go that way! Ma'am, not this way.
找掩护
Take cover.
-他在干嘛  -他在加速
- Whoa, what is he doing? - He's building up speed.
他要用声波摧毁它
He's gonna use a sonic punch to destroy it.
根据卫星的质量和它的加速下落
Given the satellite's mass and its escalating descent,
如何确保它不会摧毁他
what prevents it from destroying him?
你做的很棒  现在  我需要用力一推  好吗
You're doing great. Now, I need one big push, okay?
一  二  三
One, two, three.
她来啦
Here she comes.
巴里
Barry.
天呐
Oh, my gosh.
这可以修复你朋友的大脑
This will restore your friend's mind.
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要补偿的还有好多
I have a lot to make amends for.
你知道  马尔利泽
You know, Marlize,
还有很多的超能力者
there are still a lot of metas out there.
我是说  我们
I mean, we--
我们需要你的帮助
We could use your help.
你们已经有了足够的帮助
You have all the support you need.
而其他人真的需要我的帮助
There are those, however, that do need my help.
加入我去世的丈夫的阵营之前
Before I joined my late husband's crusade,
我用技术使一无所有的人们
I used technology to better the lives of those
过上更好的生活
who had nothing.
那时我的机械发明是在治愈世界
Back then my mechanical creations healed the world,
而不是伤害世界
not harmed it.
我要继续我未完的事业
I'll just pick up where I left off.
祝你好运
Well, good luck.
谢谢
Thank you.
-祝你好运  -再见
- Good luck. - Bye.
她不惜一切去救他
She risked everything to try and save him.
她真的爱他
She really loved him.
她内心会永远爱他
Part of her always will.
怎么了
What is it?
最后的卫星
The last satellite,
不只是我把它干掉的
it wasn't just me who took it down.
还有其他人
There was someone else.
谁  是谁
Who? Who was it?
其他极速者
Another speedster.
坚持住  哈里  快了
Hang on, Harry. We're almost there.
好  戴上这个
Okay. Now put this on.
-他还好吗  -他的脉搏稳定
- Is he okay? - His vitals are stable.
程序完成了  应该会有用
The program completed. It should have worked.
哈里
Hey, Harry.
Hey. Harry.
哈里
Harry?
别担心
Don't worry.
你一直是也永远是
You have been and will always be...
我的朋友
my friend.
杀了他们
Kill them.
天呐
Oh, my God.
《星球大战》
"Star Wars."
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
Oh, I can't believe it.
不是每天都能把符号
It's not every day you translate symbols
转换成二元多项式编程
into binary programming polynomials.
我不知道这是什么意思
I--I don't know what that means.
你知道
Yes, you do.
我真的不知道  我不知道那是什么意思
Actually, I don't. I don't know what that means.
我觉得这儿可能有点短路
I think some short circuit's been fried up here,
但没事
but it's fine.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我只是不理解
I mean, I just don't understand the--
那  你说的那话
the pol--the thing you said.
但没事
It's okay though.
怎么回事
What's the matter?
马尔利泽说可以修复啊
Marlize said this would work.
是修复了
It did work.
拉蒙  你做到了
Ramon, you did it.
我回来了  我在这啊
I'm back, I'm here.
可能和之前相比
I mean, maybe I'm a little more average
我更普通了  但我回来了
than I used to be up there, but I'm here.
哈里  你可不普通啊
Harry, there's nothing average about you.
你有七个博士学位
You have seven PhDs.
不再有了
Well, not anymore.
-我应该弄好的  -怎么回事
- I was supposed to fix this. - What's the matter?
-你做到了  拉蒙  -我没有
- And you did, Ramon. - I didn't--
拉蒙  你做到了  你做到了
Ramon, you did. You did.
你帮我恢复记忆了  你恢复了重要的东西
You brought me back. You brought back what matters.
所以那又怎样  我的整个人生
So what if I'm-- look, my whole life,
我都被一样东西所定义
I've been defined by one thing--
我的智商  但你给予我了
my IQ--and somehow you've given me, uh,
一种平衡
a balance...
平衡了我大脑和
between my head and--
谢谢你给我的平衡  拉蒙
Thank you for the balance, Ramon.
我现在要把这种平衡带到我的地球上
Now I'm going to take that balance to my Earth.
-什么  -等下  哈里
- Huh? - Wait, Harry.
哈里  我们刚见到你
Harry, we just-- we just got you back.
不  我知道  爱瑞丝
No, I know, Iris.
我得去见我女儿
I have to go see my daughter.
我也许没有拿下七个博士学位的智力
I mean, I might not have the intelligence to garner seven PhDs,
但我看清了一件事
but I can see one thing clearly.
家人最重要
Family matters.
我们也是家人
Well, we're family too.
你们当然是
Heck yeah, you are.
你们每一个
Each and every one of you.
我会想念你们的
I'll miss you.
就这样
Okay.
不清楚
I don't know.
-我们应该拥抱的  -我...
- We should probably hug. - I was like--
是的
Yeah.
我会想念你们的
I'll miss you.
-爱你们  -也爱你
- Love you guys. - Love you too.
我也爱你
I love you too.
在多元宇宙中有上万个哈里
There could be a million Harrys in this multiverse,
但你是独一无二的
but you... are one of a kind.
我也爱你
I love you too.
是一个时代的终结
It's the end of an era.
她来了
There she is.
天啊
Oh, man.
乔  她真漂亮
Joe, she's beautiful.
就像她妈妈一样
Just like her mother.
我认为应该举杯庆祝
I think this calls for a toast.
我说举杯庆祝一下
I said, this calls for a toast.
-抱歉  我...  -我拿着了
- Sorry, I was-- - I got it, I got it.
-沃利  -你不会认为我会错过
- Wally! - You didn't think I'd miss
我的新妹妹的第一个聚会吧
my new baby sister's first party, right?
好的
All right,
敬闪电小队最新的成员
to the newest member of Team Flash.
詹娜·玛丽·韦斯特
Jenna Marie West.
欢迎加入大家庭
Welcome to the family.
干杯
Cheers.
派对不错  能见到所有人真好
Nice party. It's so good to see everyone.
我听说传奇们也有
You know, I heard that the Legends
相当棒的派对
have quite some parties too.
告诉我
So, tell me,
你找到你想要的了吗
did you find what you were looking for?
找到了  而且更多
Yeah, I did. And a lot more.
我觉得对抗时间魔鬼有帮助
I think fighting a time-demon helped.
爸  我离开闪电小队是因为
But, Dad, look, I left Team Flash cause I felt
我觉得我永远会是巴里的小跟班
like I was always gonna be in Barry's shadow.
但是作为传奇一员
But as a Legend, I--
我学会了怎样做自己
I learned how to be comfortable just being me.
我为你感到骄傲  儿子
I'm so proud of you, son.
谢谢
Thank you.
-我们来看你的妹妹  -好的
- Let's see your sister. - Yes.
你好  小宝贝
Hi, handsome.
哈里说得对
Oh, you know Harry was right.
这是最重要的
This is really all that matters.
接下来就是我们了
We're next, you know?
等等  你想...什么意思
Wait, you want to have-- what do you mean?
你想现在就要孩子
You want to have a baby now?
什么意思  现在吗
What do you mean? Right now?
-巴里  -什么
- Barry. - What?
-放松  -我没事
- Relax. - I'm fine.
真的吗  我只是说有一天
Are you? I just meant someday.
好吧
Yeah.
最近不会
Not anytime in the near future.
-好  -天啊
- Right. - Oh my God.
我再给你拿杯酒放松一下
Let me just get you a refill so you can relax.
可以  谢谢
That's nice. Thanks.
-我们得谈谈  -什么
- We need to talk. - What?
房间布置不错
Wow, this house is bitchin'.
我觉得我之前见过你
I think I've seen you before.
你是不是把咖啡洒在我和哈里身上
Didn't you spill coffee all over Harry and me?
她付了你的咖啡钱吗  因为她付了我们的
Yeah, did she pay for yours? Because she paid for ours.
你是婚礼上的服务员吗
Weren't you the server at their wedding?
等等  你是
Wait, yeah, you were.
你从哪得到的这件夹克
And where did you get this jacket?
从她那里
From her.
不  我的是独一无二的
No, mine--mine is one of a kind.
这件是  当你借给我的时候
So was this, uh, when you let me borrow it.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是你的女儿  诺拉
I'm your daughter, Nora.
来自未来
From the future.
我觉得
And I think I...
我犯了大错误
made a big, big, mistake.